welcome back to another shop cut video
欢迎回到另一个商店剪辑视频
editing tutorial in this video we're
编辑教程在这段视频中我们
going to be learning how to increase the
将学习如何增加
speed that our clip is played back so we
我们回放剪辑的速度 所以我们
can do slow motion we can do fast speed
我们可以做慢动作 也可以做快动作
and so I'll show you how to do that you
所以我会告诉你怎么做 你
may have noticed so I have a video
可能已经注意到了 所以我有一段视频
brought in here on my timeline if you've
在我的时间线上带到这里如果你
been looking at filters maybe you've
一直在看过滤器 也许你已经
already tried to type in speed to look
已尝试输入速度以查看
for a speed or a slow filter or effect
对于速度或慢滤镜或效果
and you're not finding it well that's
你发现它不是很好 这是
because it's treated a little bit
因为它被稍微治疗了一下
differently in shot kit it's actually
与射击套件不同的是 它实际上是
under properties so when our clip is
在属性下 因此当我们的剪辑
selected and has read around it we're
精选并阅读了它 我们正在
gonna see the properties of whatever
会看到任何东西的属性
clip is selected and it's only the clip
剪辑处于选中状态 并且只有该剪辑
that's selected so if we were to cut
它被选中了 所以如果我们要削减
this split this clip we'd have to change
把这段视频分开 我们就得改变
the speed twice but we see there's
速度是原来的两倍 但我们看到
information about the video the audio
有关视频和音频的信息
some metadata and right up above it all
一些元数据 最重要的是
is this speed so we can change the speed
这个速度是为了让我们可以改变速度吗
here if we change this to two it's going
在这里 如果我们把这个改成两个 它就会
to be 200% or two times the speed and
以200%或两倍的速度
hit enter and then we see our clip it
按Enter键 然后我们将看到我们的剪辑
gets sort and all of a sudden and it did
得到了排序 突然之间 它做到了
the audio and the video adjusted the
音频和视频调整了
speed so it's playing very fast now we
速度 所以现在我们玩得很快
can't see this the settings up here
我看不到这里的设置
because nothing is selected when we went
因为我们去的时候没有选择任何东西
to play it D selected it for some reason
为了播放它D出于某种原因选择了它
so we left click on it again and we can
所以我们再次点击它 我们就可以
see we can change it back to one and hit
看 我们可以把它改回1 然后点击
enter put it back to where it was or we
回车 把它放回原处 否则我们
can make it down to whatever we want so
我们想做什么就做什么 所以
we can do half speed would be 0.5 hit
我们可以做一半的速度就会被击中0.5
enter and now it's half the speed so we
进入 现在速度减半 所以我们
go back to the beginning or any point
返回到起点或任何点
and we play it
我们玩这个游戏
there's a cool song Jolene by Dolly
多莉有一首很酷的歌《乔琳》
Parton it's awesome you should check it
帕顿 太棒了 你应该去看看
out they slowed it down and it sounds
他们放慢了速度 听起来
like I love listening to that song this
就像我喜欢听这首歌一样
little motion version anyway this just
小小的动作版 反正这只是
reminded me of that so yeah that's
让我想起了这一点 所以是的
basically adjusting speed what did I say
基本上是在调整速度 我说什么来着？
yeah this is basically it that's how you
是的 基本上就是这样
do speed in clips and then if we were to
在剪辑中进行速度 然后如果我们要
split this we can change the speed back
分裂这个我们可以把速度改回来
to one on this one but just be aware
这一点上的一个 但请注意
that if we do that it's only on the
如果我们这样做 那只是在
active clip so this will still be slow
活动剪辑 因此这仍然会很慢
motion and then it goes back normal
运动然后恢复正常
speed if we split it again and change
如果我们再次分裂并改变 速度
this one to three times the speed well
这个一到三倍的速度好
now we're gonna have slow regular and
现在我们将有缓慢的常规
then fast speed that's it basically I
然后速度快 基本上就是这样
guess I don't need to say any more
想我不需要再说了
adjusting speed using shot good thanks
使用镜头调整速度很好 谢谢
for watching catch you in the next video
供观看下一个视频中抓住你